<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ISILAB</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ISILAB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:29:06 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/starting-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:29:06 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/starting-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/screenshots/lbs_01.png&#34; data-dimbox data-dimbox-caption=&#34;alt text&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/assets/screenshots/lbs_01.png&#34; alt=&#34;alt text&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;level-building-sidekick&#34;&gt;Level Building Sidekick&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LBS is an extension designed for Unity Engine, which facilitates developers in creating environments for their video games, thereby contributing to increased productivity. This extension features artificial intelligence assistants in various areas, which suggest modifications based on the fundamental characteristics developed by the user. These suggestions enable developers to explore new possibilities without manually creating these variations, fostering greater creative freedom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Level Building Sidekick (LBS) is a tool that allows software developers to define the architecture, constraints, graphical elements, and decorative details that will be used in the construction of a level for video games and other areas. This process enables increased team productivity and the quality and diversity of content they can offer to their users. The tool allows artists to upload any assets they have created for their projects, enabling them to compose custom asset sets for different genres, sections, or styles. LBS is a mixed-initiative content generation tool focused on creating content such as levels, population, and missions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
